<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>abm</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on abm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:39:15 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parsing Elf and Dwarf Files on Linux with the Zig Standard Library: Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/programming/parsing-elf-and-dwarf-files-on-linux-with-the-zig-standard-library-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:39:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/programming/parsing-elf-and-dwarf-files-on-linux-with-the-zig-standard-library-part1/</guid>
      <description>Background Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty into debuggers. With the recent development of the RAD Debugger Project, RemedyBG&amp;rsquo;s continued existence, and smaller projects like Spray, I became interested in how they work under the hood. So I set out to try to craft a (simple) debugger on my own. Unfortunately, I decided to start at the harder part of crafting a debugger, parsing ELF and DWARF. Ok, to be fair, they are not ESPECIALLY difficult, but there is a severe lack of resources available on the subject (please correct me if I&amp;rsquo;m wrong here).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Tmux Guide I Wish I Had</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/programming/the-tmux-guide-i-wish-i-had/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 23:32:15 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/programming/the-tmux-guide-i-wish-i-had/</guid>
      <description>GENERAL: tmux: start session exit: leave session&#xA;default prefix key: ctrl-b copy mode: prefix + [ select area to copy: ctrl-v + space&#xA;PANES: contain individual terminal sessions only one active at a time vsplit: ctrl-b + % hsplit: ctrl-b + “ change window: ctrl-b + &amp;lt;up, down, left, right move pane: ctrl-b + { or } select pane by number: ctrl-b + q + [PANE_NUMBER] zoom into pane: ctrl-b + z make pane a window: ctr-b + !</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nu Program 3.0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/health/nu-program-3_0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:25:27 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/health/nu-program-3_0/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Font and SDF Rect Rendering With Zig and WGPU</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/programming/font-and-sdf-rect-rendering-with-zig-and-wgpu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:21:28 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/programming/font-and-sdf-rect-rendering-with-zig-and-wgpu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Ive Been Practicing - 001</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/music/what-ive-been-practicing-001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 23:20:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/music/what-ive-been-practicing-001/</guid>
      <description>A Little Background Since coming home from school, I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot more time to practice the drums (yay)! For context, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing the drum set since 7th grade. I started off learning West African drumming, the steel pans and even traditional Japanese taiko drumming. In high school, I played in Jazz Band, Gospel Band, Symphonic Band, and even the marching band as a snare drummer. I thought I would not play in college, but I was convinced by a friend of mine to audition for an on-campus, R&amp;amp;B/Jass/Hip-Hop group called &amp;ldquo;Love, and a Sandwich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howdy, world!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/howdy-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:45:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/howdy-world/</guid>
      <description>Howdy, world. My name is Bryson Miller, and this is my personal website. Here I will be discussing topics in the fields of programming, music, and health.&#xA;Since I just graduated from college, I have a lot more free time now. I also have lot of thoughts™. This blog will mainly serve as a one-off dumping ground for any interesting problems/solutions or ideas that I&amp;rsquo;ve come across while going about my day job or hobby projects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:41:15 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Bryson Miller: Software Engineer based in SF. Interested in low-level programming, performance, systems. Outside of programming I love drumming and working out.&#xA;Find me on GitHub (code) and Youtube (long form educational content).&#xA;Powered by Hugo using the Basics theme.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
